As you see, Photo Image Editor is being loaded for us,
wants to show me notifications, I don't want that for now.
But as you see, so when it comes to Photo Editing,
when it comes to Photo Editor,
first we need to have a photo,
and then we want to edit that very photo that we have,
if that makes sense, you know?
And this is why every single photo editor that we want to use,
first it asks us to upload an image.
So this is going to be the image that
we're going to make the edit song, right?
And as you see,
so let me click on Upload Image
and choose an image, for example, yep, this one.
For a better idea, let's use the very photo
that Photo Generated for us.
So I go to my library,
and I want to download the photo,
and then add it to the Photo Editor
to be able to make my edits, if that makes sense.
And as you see, my library is opened over here,
so I come and click on this creation of mine,
I download it,
and yes.
So I come to the Photo Editor right now,
and again, click on Upload Image,
but this time, I come to my desktop,
and this is the photo that I'm going to use,
as you see, Photo Creation, 2025, 12, 4.
So I double-click, in order to open it up,